buzzle.com 2005-12-31

# Buzzle Privacy Policy

At Buzzle.com, we respect the privacy of people who visit our website. Because we gather information from our visitors, we know something about them even after they leave. Here is what you can expect from us regarding information we gather from you: 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Buzzle.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Buzzle.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

_We use your information to improve our website_  
Buzzle.com uses information for responding to requests, customizing services and generally improving communications with visitors. 

For example, we store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. This information is gathered through "cookies," which help us communicate with you when you visit our website again. 

_We do not sell your information to others_  
Buzzle.com does not sell customer lists or personal information it gathers to other businesses or individuals. However, we may share generalized information about visitors to improve our website. 

For example, we may compile numbers and frequency of visits to determine the types of services our visitors use most. We may use this information to sell advertising on our website and help visitors obtain more services or products. 

_We are not responsible for others who use your information_  
Buzzle.com does not take responsibility for information that others may gather about visitors through its website. 

For example, other individuals or businesses may gather information about you when you follow a hyperlink from our website to theirs. We are not responsible for those individuals or businesses. 

_We may use your information if you consent_  
Buzzle.com may use information about visitors in the future, if they consent. 

For example, we may upgrade our website to offer more services or products. We may notify you by email of such upgrades, and ask you for permission to send you more information in the future. 

**Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Games, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**  
This web site contains thousands of links to other sites. Please be aware that we Buzzle.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Buzzle.com Magazines**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our magazines, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

**Surveys and Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Buzzle.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Buzzle.com does not store this information other than for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, contact us. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. 

For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user's credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed. 

(or) 

In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these partners, the partners collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences. 

**Special Offers**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and newsletters. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by contacting us. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our magazines or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by editing the appropriate information in the Magazines Subscriptions 

**Management area**  
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

You may contact us if you have concerns about your information At Buzzle.com, we want to ensure visitors that their privacy is protected. If you have a concern about your privacy, please contact us.
